- Tell me you want me.
- Not right now.
Well,
I'm gonna have incredible sex
with whoever's next
to walk out of that bathroom.
- He's hot.
- He's a New York City seven.
- Tops.
- Oh, well I'll be damned
if he ain't an Amtrak ten.
- Give me one thing.
- Fine. I'm a senior architect.
Fiona, I don't wanna do this
anymore. It's over.
- Ruby. Ruby.
- Sit down, ya lightweight?
I used to drink his ass
under the table when I was 19.
Everyone can see
you're not 19 anymore.
- Where... Where are you going?
- Oh, I'm going home.
I have a life with consequences,
and thank God
that we didn't do anything
that I can't take back.
Hi, there.
You've reached the Richardsons.
If you're looking for Ruby,
she ran out
on her family yesterday.
We don't know where she is,
why she left,
or when she's coming back.
Have a great day.
Woman:
Ruby!
Ruby: Coming.
I just had
a collision with the Wall.
- Stop calling her that.
- She had the temerity
to ask me why you were speaking
at the wedding breakfast.
- Oh God.
- I said you were speaking
because you have
a goddamn voice.
- You did not say that.
- No.
I said that her son
was not a misogynist.
Okay, let's do this.
Step... Oh!
Kelly is here.
- What?
- Yeah, she's outside.
I swear, I-I didn't
tell Dad that he could...
I know.
He brought her anyway.
It's all right.
It's better now that
it's out in the open.
Believe me. It's better.
I wanted to give you something.
This is insanely expensive
and you cannot afford it.
- Is it the one you wanted?
- Yes, when I was
in college, yes.
- But that was...
- A big-shot architect
will need a big-shot pen.
Has he texted today?
Let's go.
No! What I'm...
What I'm saying is
I did have a ticket...
But, you no longer have it.
Correct! So... ooh.
- Should th-that be cool?
- No!
She's being honest,
believe it or not.
One of the only people
I ever met who
sounds like she's lying
when she's telling the truth.
I like you better already.
You're sexier.
You're stronger. You're funnier.
You're smashing your career.
You...
You seem so much better.
And that scares the shit
out of me because...
I think I might be worse.
- One day.
- What?
Gimme one day.
Turn off your phone.
- Here. Give it to me.
- No. Okay! Okay!
- You turn your own phone off.
- I can turn my own phone off!
You said that I don't know you.
So let's have one more
day together here,
and at the end, we can decide
to get back on the train and
continue our journey together,
or we can go our separate ways,
but we don't decide
till the end of the day.
What do you say?
Yeah.
Announcement:
The 8:00 AM train
to Los Angeles
is about to depart.
Wait, I don't get what time
the next train comes.
Hang on.
Hey, no phones!
Man:
Architecture tour?
- Thank you.
- No problem.
Hey. How do you know
that? Are you...?
Are you tracking
my credit cards?
Yeah, I am,
and it doesn't mean
that I'm meeting you.
No, you won't because
it's a huge fucking city.
Okay, fine, fine. Just shut
up and I'll meet you then.
It's 24 hours till
the next train!
I mean, there's one a day.
Yikes.
We're gonna have
to get a hotel room.
One hotel room?
Ms. Dixie,
where am I to sleep?
Let's get it now.
- Now?
- Yeah.
I wanna fuck you.
Now.
You know you can't undo that.
I don't wanna unfuck you.
I don't wanna unfuck you either.
A lot of conferences in town,
but we have the Alpha Suite,
one of our Deluxe Premier rooms
with a full river
view at $1,200.
So, I wanna get it, but, um,
my cards have all stopped
working for some reason.
No, I'll get it.
I just...
I don't have a credit card.
- I-I don't believe in them.
- Tinkerbell,
they do exist whether you
believe in them or not.
Welcome to the Brock Hotel.
No, no, no! W-wait!
We're taking the room!
I've got this.
When will you be
cashing that, please?
We don't accept those.
Would you...
hold the room with it
while we go and get the cash?
Amara, we are next in the line,
and we would like you
to hold the room
with this check while
we go and get the cash.
Please.
- Who was that?
- I don't know.
I think I just
turned into my mother.
- How is Mary?
- Aw.
- Angry.
- Amara: I'll need you
to have the cash
by 3:00.
- Hey! Easy.
- Which is when
you'll get the room.
Ah. Um,
that's five hours away.
Aw, would you like to cancel?
- Nope.
- No. 3:00 is fine.
- Morning. Sean, is it?
- Good morning.
- You're Irish?
- I am. Yeah.
I'm a little Irish.
Would you go way outta that?
And a very Irish name
you have too. Listen,
Sean, I have a question for you.
If someone knows
all your details,
like your security number,
your passwords,
all that sort of malarkey,
can they withdraw money
- from your account online?
- Uh, no.
Online, we ask
a series of questions
that you would've answered
when you first set it up.
Okay, so the person
in question knows
- fucking everything about me.
- Oh, well, in that case,
then yeah.
Okay, I need to
withdraw the money
in this account please, Sean.
All of it, please.
- Uh, when you say...
- Just, uh, just in
here would be deadly.
Sean:
Uh, I-I'm sorry,
but we can't process that
request at this time.
- Please...
- $1,000 is the most
you can withdraw...
Please don't tell me
I can't, Sean.
Me old flower, you are
literally me last hope.
Uh, the amount in this account
is what we would call
a large sum of money...
Ah, come on now...
So if we were to release
the funds, we would need to
fill out a number of forms,
my manager would have
to come down
and sign everything,
and then you
would have to come
back later today.
Is there any fecking way at all
I could talk to your manager
ahead of time then, Sean?
Well, no, uh,
because my manager takes
my advice on his decision.
Fair enough.
- And you'll make sure it's
safe until I come back?
- Yeah, absolutely.
Assuming you're approved.
Ruby:
Four hours to go. Ugh!
This is torture.
Billy:
I know.
Ruby:
So, if it was 17 years ago,
what would you
be doing right now?
Oh. Uh,
I'd have to go
back to campus soon
'cause I have
an essay due tomorrow
for English 220 on
As I Lay Dying.
But I don't wanna write it
'cause I'm in the city
with my girlfriend.
Ruby:
Have you even started the essay?
Billy:
Oh no, fuck no. I haven't
even started the book.
But my soon-to-be-qualified
architect girlfriend's
gonna help me with it,
and, uh, she's...
valedictorian, so...
Oh man.
You even still smell like you.
- What do I smell like?
- I don't know.
I smelled it in Boots
a few years ago.
I thought, "That's Ruby.
She must be right
around that corner."
And you weren't.
So it turns out, you smell like
the moisturizer aisle in Boots.
What is Boots?
It's a...
a chain pharmacy.
There's one in every town.
Wow. I mean,
thank you very much.
Shit. Okay.
We have to go now.
Go where?
- Come on. Come on.
- Billy...
Where are we going?
Tour Guide:
On the right,
we have the Wrigley Building,
headquarters of
the chewing gum empire.
- Modeled after...
- Ruby: Well, now I feel guilty.
-You love it?
All the buildings!
-Yes!
- It's so sweet of you.
- Yeah.
I wanna say something.
It's taken me, like,
14 hours to be able to say it...
15 years,
14 hours, but I'm
finally ready to say it.
Here goes.
You were right.
There, I said it.
Don't make me tell you
what about... All right!
All right! I'll tell you.
You were right about leaving me.
Never thought
I'd be able to say that.
I always thought,
well, she better have a pretty
fuckin' amazing career
after what she did to that
beautiful relationship of ours.
But you do. You did it,
so hats off to you.
Tour Guide:
And now here on the right,
the Tribune Tower,
the preeminent example
of Gothic architecture
here in Chicago.
What makes a building Gothic?
You know, listens to sad music,
wears black eyeliner...
When I first saw you,
you were wearing
all the black eyeliner.
I'm not an architect.
What?
I started the program
and I just...
I couldn't do it.
It was my first job, and...
I started getting
panic attacks at the thought
of going to work.
I kept trying to be
the me I was...
when I was with you.
You always said I was great.
I was not great, and...
when they fired me,
I pretended to go in.
By the time
I stopped pretending...
I was in quite a mess.
And then I got married.
I guess at the time
that I met him,
I needed what he gave me.
You still with him?
Uh-huh.
Do you love him?
When we watch movies,
he wants me to...
sit really still
and quiet.
- You're kidding.
- Well, it sounds
worse than it is.
- Although, you are,
actually, quite annoying.
- What?
Yeah, you talking
through a movie
was one of our biggest fights.
I don't remember us fighting.
We fought...
all the time.
Laurence and I
never fight, really.
But I argue with
him inside my head.
And I always used to fantasize
that I was two people.
The normal one
that lived with him...
and then this fun
person who went out...
and had sex...
and did all this
drunken crazy shit
like you were probably doing.
Probably.
Wait, why did you fantasize
you were two people?
Why not just the fun one?
Well, I don't know.
And then, you know,
the usual story.
You wake up and...
it's 12 years later.
I feel like you skipped
quite a bit there.
We said no phones.
We did. I'm an eejit.
I totally forgot.
- Turn it off. Now.
- Okay.
I'm turning it off.
I'm sorry.
Well, go on then.
It's nearly hotel o'clock.
Oh. It's two hours away.
- Let's get fancy clothes.
- What?
Let's get all dressed up
in fancy clothes.
Well, I guess underwear
would be a good idea.
What kind of underwear?
That's my business.
Hey!
- Ruby: This is nice.
- Billy: Ooh. That is nice.
Oh! Not that nice.
Wait, wait, wait!
Buy it.
It'll look great on you.
- It's $600.
- It's a special night.
We're in Chicago.
We're together.
This is a dream.
Okay, look, I'm gonna go away
in search of man pants,
and I'm not talking
about trousers,
so I'll see you back
inside our hotel in 94 minutes.
Okay?
Billy!
My husband...
froze all my cards
and I don't have
an independent income.
It's okay.
- Whoa, whoa! What is that?
- Just take that.
Buy yourself something
nice with it.
That sounds like
a dirty old man.
Buy yourself something or
don't buy yourself something,
but please take it because
I know how shit it feels
- to be stranded.
- Okay.
That's... Th-thank you. Whoa.
Bye!
Ooh!
Oh no!
Help!
- Woman: Are you stuck?
- Ruby: I'm so stuck!
Look, I think it goes like this.
- Are you sure?
- Yeah. Just let me, okay?
Oh! Oh! Are my tits out?
Yeah, but you got great tits,
so don't worry about it.
Free at last.
Oh, wait a second.
Oh...
Oh my God.
- I can't believe
I just did that.
- No.
I mean, you can pull up
your own trousers.
Thank you so much
for helping me.
So embarrassing.
- Hi.
- I'm Ruby.
- I'm Alice.
Hm.
Okay, this dress
was disastrous on me,
but you should try it.
- It's my size.
- Then try it on.
- Looks expensive.
- It is.
Well, no slip of material
is worth this much money.
Exactly,
which is why we have...
- What are you doing?!
- Shh!
Go get changed.
Hey.
I'm here at my own massive
inconvenience, so where are you?
Ruby:
I can't do it. I can't do it.
I can't do it!
Alice:
Yes, you can, yes, you can.
When I say run. Ready? Run!
Oh, God!
Oh my God, that was so exciting!
I stole a dress!
I stole sneakers!
I would just never do
something like that!
Oh, I feel incredible!
I feel so...
Oh my, oh my God!
I've run away from my kids!
What?
I've run away with an ex
who I haven't seen in forever!
And we've got this room
at the Brock Hotel!
And I left my kids
with my husband,
and they're my babies,
and I miss them so much!
But I just needed to see!
I needed to see!
You just left them for a guy?
D-don't judge me!
I know! I'm awful!
But am I awful? See,
I don't know what I want.
- Well, what triggered it?
- Um...
My husband wanted me to
wait in for his speakers.
Oh my God.
That's not a reason, is it?
Look, maybe if you're
feeling that bad about it,
maybe you should go home?
- You think?
- I do!
But, the day isn't over.
- The day?
- Well, we said we'd
take a day to decide.
Oh! Well, if it's
just for a day...
- You think?
- Yeah, do it!
- Hey, you know what
would be amazing?
- What?
For you to have a gorgeous bath
in that beautiful bathroom.
Have you seen it?
- Now?
- Yeah! Come have a look!
- Do I stink?
- No.
So, let me go down and
get us some room service,
and you can have a lovely bath,
and that way, we won't
have to stop all evening.
Room service comes to
the room, doesn't it?
Not anymore.
They make you go and get it
in these big hotels.
- Really?
- Yeah.
Fucking bullshit. Um...
Okay, I'll see you in 20.
Mother... cunt.
Stay outta my fuckin' phone.
Man:
that's the nicest thing
anyone's ever said to me.
Don't worry.
She doesn't mean it.
You found me!
Why the fuck are
you stalking me?
Listen, you've taken a couple
of days off, but it's...
- It's not just a couple days.
- Then what the fuck is it?
Did I not make it
clear on the phone?
I'm not doing the tour.
Then you're gonna be facing
some very serious lawsuits.
I will deal with that.
This is no longer your concern.
- What's this?
- It's 10 grand.
- Billy...
- It's, I-I thought...
- How can you be so...
- Shh...
Don't fucking shush me.
Look, we're a team, all right?
We're not an equal team.
I do all the work,
- you get all the praise,
but we are a team.
- Wel... Exactly.
The only good thing about this
mess is that it made me realize
I hate what we did together
with all my heart.
You're brilliant.
You'll get another job.
Yeah, but that's
just it, Billy. I...
I won't get another job
because all you ever made me
-was your fucking PA.
I won't be fucking fine!
-You'll be fine...
I'm your COO in all but name.
I built this company
from nothing with you,
and I haven't even
made any plans
because of all the dedication
that was required.
I haven't met anyone.
I haven't started a family.
Officially,
I'm trained in nothing,
so if I wanted cash, Billy,
I'd want a hell of a lot more
than this before I let
you forget about me.
Just saying.
I'm leaving now.
Oh...
Do you trust me?
I think...
I deserve an explanation.
The moratorium's finally over.
Fuck the moratorium.
Okay.
Do you wanna be here with me,
or is this about something else?
- You have a husband.
- I've been totally
honest with you.
Is anyone totally honest?
Are you using me, Billy?
N... No, I'm not using you.
Ask me anything.
I'll tell you the truth.
Are you in trouble?
Billy:
Yeah.
- Are you a bank robber?
- It's my money.
Most people don't carry around
a giant bag of their own money.
I know. But I made
a huge mistake, so...
Uh-uh.
I have this money
because I fucked up in my job.
People are very mad at me,
and so I'm taking my money
because I can't ever go back.
Everyone knows
I'm full of shit...
- and I don't know what to do.
- What happened?
Three days ago,
I'm at my biggest ever event.
Pre-sold, full capacity,
hundreds of people with...
more shows pre-sold
to thousands more.
And as part of my show,
right in the beginning,
I pull someone up from the crowd
and they tell me their problem.
I give them a few words,
and they're happy.
The crowd's happy,
and we're off to a great start.
So, I pull someone up.
Nice woman,
lovely smile. Jackie.
And Jackie says that
her beloved husband,
Brad, died a few weeks ago.
So, I go into
condolence mode, but no.
She doesn't want that
because the reason
Brad died, she says,
is because he killed himself
as a result of
a mental breakdown
shortly after
coming off his meds.
And the reason Brad
came off his meds,
according to Jackie,
is because I told him to.
- You didn't say that?
- Not literally, no.
- Not literally?
- And so, I started to sweat.
And I heard this voice...
It was my voice, but it
was, like, disembodied,
like it was somebody
else's voice, you know?
And I think it said,
"Do you know what, Jackie?
"You're right.
"Who am I to be preaching
at you like this?
"I'm a 37-year-old man
"without a life or a girlfriend
"or even a proper home.
I'm a fuckin' fraud,
"and I am as guilty of
your husband's death
as if I had killed him myself."
And then I told
them all to go home.
And this was...
10 minutes into
a three-day event,
by the way,
so that went down well.
And now, there are memes of me,
and I think I'm just
becoming like a bit of a...
- A laughingstock.
- Scapegoat.
- Um... Yeah.
- Huh?
No, I guess laughingstock's
about right.
If you want to go home,
I'll understand.
But I'll tell you one thing,
absolutely honestly.
I really don't want you to.
Ruby: Oh, Billy.
Oh, Billy.
Where are we?
Oh, my God.
- Laurence, I'm sorry.
- I don't want sorry.
Are you having
another breakdown?
Are you following me?
My friend that I met
at the department store...
- She's on the train.
- What does she look like?
Short, pretty, dark hair.
He has this big bag of money.
Ruby,
you don't know him anymore.
I wasn't totally honest with you
about what happened on stage.